== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Sheldon:)Hello.
Oh!
(Amy:)What are you doing here?
(Sheldon:)When last we spoke,
you said you needed time.
(Amy:)Well, it's only been 11 hours.
The Lord of the Rings trilogy
was nearly 11 hours.
(Sheldon:)I made you watch that,
you said it was an eternity.
(Amy:)Sheldon, when I'm ready to talk,
I'll let you know.
(Sheldon:)Very well.
(Sheldon:)You seem to be
headed somewhere.
(Sheldon:)May I walk with you?
(Amy:)Sure.
(Sheldon:)Boy, I'm glad we're
going out again.
(Amy:)We're not back together.
(Leonard:)Why?
(Sheldon:)Is there someone else?
(Sheldon:)Just couldn't wait
for that first notch
(Sheldon:)on your bedpost, could you?
(Amy:)If you must know,
(Amy:)I'm going to Howard
and Bernadette's
(Amy:)to watch the wedding.
(Sheldon:)And who's this guy
you're taking?
There's no guy!
(Sheldon:)Oh, you're going
to a wedding alone?
(Sheldon:)That's sad.
(Amy:)I'm not gonna be alone.
(Amy:)I'll be with my friends.
Your friends?